ACTWU Labor Unity Photograph Files 5981 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: LABOR UNITY
  - Fonda, Jane. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Includes: Jane Fonda supporting J.P. Stevens boycott, in front of display and with placard, also Includes article written by Fonda.
  - Food Stamps., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Includes: men and women from Food Stamp Story 4/77.
  - Football Players., 1978-1987 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Includes: ACTWU solidarity rally with NFL players, Veterans Stadium Philadelphia 10/7/87, New England Patriots including Mosi Tatupu picketing in Fall River Mass. for ILGWU Local 178 10/5/78.
  - Ford, Gerald. Portrait from TV screen, portrait as VP, giving State of Union address. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Ford Motor Company. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Includes: group shot of Harry Bennett directed Ford anti-union army.
  - Foreign Visitors. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Includes: group shots of ACTWU display and behind table.
  - Foreman, Carol Tucker (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Includes: portrait.
  - Fox, John. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Includes: portrait; receiving Histadrut Distinguished Service Award with Congressman William H. Gray III, S. Henry Galfand, Nicholas DiPiero, Sheinkman, Eliezer Rafaeli and Irwin Solomon; and visiting Rep. William Gray re: imports.
  - Fox, Sam., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Includes: group shots from Retirement dinner with Bud Clark, in Hong Kong with Gauthier and Vesnaven, portrait, at podium at Montreal Ins & Pension Fund Dinner, speaking after re-election 3/79, speaking at CCC convention.
  - Frank, Sol. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Fraser, Doug. (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Includes: portrait with Rev. Flemind.
  - Frazier, Carl., 1977-1982 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Includes: shots of Frazier, receiving plaque from Bud Clark in myrtle Beach, SC, at convention 1981, in office 1977, signing new contract with Local 1739 and Masland Carpet in Carlisle, Pa., group shot from Masland Carpet Strike 6/80, retirement portrait
  - Free Trade Boycott-Canada., 1986 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Includes: Group shot of picketers in costumes, Kitchener, Ont. April, 1986.
  - Friedman Marks. (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Includes: shots of Friedman Marks Clothing Co., from outside; and group shots and candid closeups of officials meeting and discussing. Negs included.
  - Frontier Hotel Demo-Las Vegas., 1993 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Includes: group shots of protest & demonstration outside Hotel.
  - Fry, Julius., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Includes: candid close-up, 4/79.
  - Full Employment., 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Includes: picture of comic, group shots of Full Employment Rally 9/10/77, with "Boycott J.P. Stevens Products" t-shirts and parade, Philadelphia, also group shots of LA F.E. rally, including Finley at F.E. Rally Committee Dinner 5/79 Wash. DC, also Corett
  - Gabrielski, Roz. close-up of/portrait. (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Gambert Shirt Co.. (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Includes: Group shot of workers holding up victory "V" or peace sign.
  - Gaines, Joe L. President Local 2280. (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth. (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Garfein, Dorothy. (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Includes: Garfein speaking about paid drug prescription program available to workers in TWUA Health Plan.
  - Garrhan, Charles J., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Includes: portrait, opening trade show with Grossman, McDavid, Scotto, Law, Linder, Faulding, O'Neal, and Avrutin; receiving award from Group Health Inc. with Levine, Grossman, Avrutin; with Rocco Campanaro and Amodeo 4/24/80 at protest breakfast against
  - Gasoline Shortage., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    Includes: shot of long gas line 1976.
  - Gaylord Container Corp. (Box 4, Folder 47b)
    Includes: individual and group shots of women and men in plant.
  - Geer, Will. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 48. Includes: shots of Geer at support rally in LA for JP Stevens workers, with Cribbs, Waite, and Fleming; with family playing Woody Guthrie union songs.
  - GEB Adopts Plan to aid Jobless Members., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 49. Includes: shot of unemployment line, GEB Bd. Meeting 5/83.
  - General Executive Board (ACTWU)., 1976-1982 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 50. Includes: group shots of ACTWU GEB meeting Baltimore w/ Dropkin, Sheinkman, etc., group shot of new VPs 1982 with Finley and Sheinkman, individual shots of Harry Lautman, Vincent Riccardelli, Paul Swaity, De
  - GEB meeting Bal Harbor, Fla. 3/77., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 51. Includes: Group shots: Miller, Sheinkman, and Finley in front of Americano logo.
  - GEB 10/77., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 52.Includes: group shots of meeting and officials including Secretary of Labor Ray Marshall, Finley, Sheinkman, Treasury Secretary Michael Blumenthal.
  - GEB 12/77., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 52b -- Includes: Group shots featuring Finley et al at meeting.
  - GEB Report- Convention (Misc.)., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 53 -- Includes: workers, pamphleteers, and an office worker.
  - GEB Meeting 3/78., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 54 -- Includes: Group shots of meeting with Mimi Denerstein, DuChessi, Sheinkman, Finley, Stetin, and Potofsky.
  - GEB Meeting- July, 1978- Quebec. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 55 -- Includes: Group shots of meeting.
  - GEB Executive Board Meeting 3/79., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 56 -- Includes: group shots with Finley, Sheinkman, Miller etc. and a Closeup of Finley with gavel.
  - GEB Meeting - 10/79., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 57 -- Includes: group shots of meeting with ACTWU officials.
  - GEB Meeting - June 1979. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 58 -- Includes: group shots of ACTWU officials at meeting and of Goldsmith, Finley, Arthur Loevy, Nocella and Stetin viewing photos celebrating 50th anniversary of Chicago and Central States Jt. Bd. HQ.
  - GEB Executive Board Meeting 3/80., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 59 -- Includes: group and individual shots of ACTWU officials.
  - General Executive Board 5/80., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 60 -- Includes: Group and individual shots of ACTWU officials at meeting.
  - GEB Meeting, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 61 -- Includes: group shots of ACTWU officials at meeting- Toronto.
  - GEB Report. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 62 -- Includes: group shot of ACTWU officials and portrait of Sheinkman.
  - GEB- May '87. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 63 -- Includes: Group shots of ACTWU officials in formal group pose.
  - GEB, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 64 -- Includes: portraits of Sheinkman (new Pres.) and Loevy (new Sec. Treasurer).
  - General Office 15 Union Square. (Box 21, Folder 19)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 65 -- Includes: inside building/office.
  - Genereaux, Denise. Individual and group shots at plant. (Box 21, Folder 20)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 66
  - Genesco and Grief Co., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 67 -- Includes: Sam Nocella speaking at protest 3/80, DeFazio & Papale also in photo.
  - Genis, Sander., 1982 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 68 Includes: group shots from retirement luncheon 1982, portrait of, and group shot with Sheinkman and Finley.
  - Georgia. (Box 21, Folder 23)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 69 Includes: portrait of Bishop Lessard, group shots of elderly in wheelchairs and group shots of ACTWU organizers.
  - Georgia-Tennessee-Alabama Jt. Bd., 1985 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 70 Includes: group shots of Jt. Bd. Meeting, Knoxville Dec. 1985, group shot of new local 2321 members w/ G-T-A Jt. Bd. Mgr. Brown, and group shots from GTA Jt. Bd. Meeting 4/85.
  - Georgian, Angelo. (Box 21, Folder 25)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 71 Includes: portraits and snapshots of Georgian at AFL-CIO podium, w/ Sheinkman, and with Fileno DeNovellis, Mrs. Georgian, Sol Stetin, Howard Brown, Joseph Huighe, Santo Pernicone, Saffiotti, Agnese, Figur
  - Georgine, Robert. (Box 21, Folder 26)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 72 Includes: portrait of.
  - Gerber, Greensboro NC., 1988 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 73 Includes: group shots of workers celebrating first contract May 1988.
  - German Trade Unionists Visit U.S. (Box 21, Folder 28)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 74 Includes: group shots of Sheinkman, Katz, Anke(sic) Fuchs, Dr. Werner Tegtmeier, Dr. Herbert Ehrenberg, Finley, Miller, and Goldstein.
  - Gibson, Harold., 1981 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 75 Includes: Gibson at podium at Convention L.U. 6/81.
  - Gitman Bros. (Box 21, Folder 30)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 76 Includes: group & individual shots of workers at Gitman Shirt Co. ACTWU Local 132 L.U. Jan-Feb '94.
  - Gits Plastic Corp. (Box 21, Folder 31)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 77 Includes: group shot of workers celebrating election victory.
  - Glazer, Joe. (Box 21, Folder 32)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 78 Includes: shot of Glazer with guitar singing at AFL-CIO podium for DuChessi Memorial, also many shots of Glazer singing and playing onstage.
  - Glenn, John. (Box 21, Folder 33)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 79 Includes: portrait, group shot with Chet Mukashi and group shot at head of IUE parade.
  - Global Builders. (Box 21, Folder 34)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 80 Includes: group shots of workers outside plant.
  - Gloversville, NY. (Box 21, Folder 35)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 80b Includes: demonstration.
  - Goldberg, Arthur. (Box 21, Folder 36)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 81 Includes: individual shots at podium and behind desk, and group shot with Sol Stetin and Paul Swaity.
  - Goldberg, Easer. (Box 21, Folder 37)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 82 Includes: portrait of Goldberg and group shot of him with office staff.
  - Golden Valet. (Box 21, Folder 38)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 83 Includes: individual and group shots of workers in shop.
  - Goldsmith, Harry. (Box 21, Folder 39)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 84 Includes: Goldsmith at podium and desk and group shot receiving Histadrut honor with Finley, Sheinkman, Benjamin Sella and Stetin.
  - Goldstein, Murray. (Box 21, Folder 40)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 85 Includes: individual shots while speaking, group shot receiving Scroll of Honor from Workman's Circle Home for the Aged.
  - Gompers, Samuel. (Box 21, Folder 41)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 86 Includes: individual shot, group shot with Sarah Conboy, Mayor Talbott, John Campos, White and James Starr, also Includes naval ship "Samuel Gompers".
  - Good Quality Sewing. (Box 21, Folder 42)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 87 Includes: shots of women working including negatives.
  - Goode, Wilson. (Box 21, Folder 43)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 88 Includes: group shot of Goode with Finley and others in front of campaign posters.
  - Gordon, Harry. (Box 21, Folder 44)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 89 Includes: group shots of Gordon with Finley, Sheinkman, and portrait with obituary.
  - Gordon, Morris. (Box 21, Folder 45)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 90 Includes: portrait of.
  - Gore, Albert. (Box 21, Folder 46)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 91 Includes: group shots of Gore with Barnhart, Raynor, Ferraris and Geneva Sneed.
  - Gore, Tipper. Group shot at Local 456. (Box 21, Folder 47)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 92
  - Grandoe Corp. (Gloversville). (Box 21, Folder 48)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 93 Includes: women working; plant scenes; workers; warehouse shots; machinery; shop.
  - Granite State Leadership Conference (Sept. 1976). (Box 21, Folder 49)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 94 Includes: Bruce Raynor, Joann Riggs, Thomas Pitarys, and Bruce Dunton at New Hampshire college.
  - Grape Boycotts. (Box 21, Folder 50)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - box 4, ff 95 Includes: contact sheets; Sheinkman at NY UAW rally.
  - Grasso, Ella. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff 96 -- Includes: signing Ella purses; Grasso/Killian propaganda; Grasso at dinner; man making gloves.
  - Greater Cornwall Jt. Bd. - Classes., 1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff97 Includes: locals 779, 1332, 1649, 1664, 1903, 1915, 2343, and 2412, January 1984; Gordon Vala-Webb conducting class at Cornwall "House of Labor".
  - Greater Cornwall Jt. Bd. (Spotlight). (Box 22, Folder 3)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff98 Includes: Riverside Yarns, Rene Vallee; Local 1664 worker; Local 2281 worker; stewards class, Roy Collins; Cornwall, Ontario Gordon Vala-Webb swears in Executive Board.
  - Greater New York Joint Board. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff99 Includes: Black men working; Black woman running blocking machine; contact sheets; office scenes; women in offices working; dental clinic, tooth filling; man operating drying machine; frame operator at Easter
  - Greater Northeastern Joint Board., 1988 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff100 Includes: Southern New England Joint Board Steward Training February 1988 Willimantic, CT; Ella Ford, Local 1362, Bristol, NH; contact sheet.
  - Greater Toronto Joint Board. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff101 Includes: Spanish dancer at banquet; convention; Ken Stonehouse gives gold watch to Mo Robillard; bargaining table at Filterfab; dinner dance, Sol Stetin; lottery drawing.
  - Green, William. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff102 Includes: Bill Green for senator; Green speaking at 25th Anniversary of Sidney Hillman Health Center, Murray H. Finley, Harry Goldsmith.
  - Greenbrier Mfg. (Organizing Story). (Box 22, Folder 8)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff103 Includes: worker meeting; women workers.
  - Greene, Edith. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff104 Includes: ACTWU paperback library; contact sheet.
  - Greenville, SC Social Services Agency Seminar., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff105 Includes: May 1979 seminar.
  - Groce, Marion E. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff106 Includes: portrait of Groce.
  - Gundersheim, Art. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff107 Includes: man speaking.
  - Guthrie, Woody (Bound for Glory). (Box 22, Folder 13)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff108 Includes: actors, director; movie scenes.
  - Greyhound. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff109 Includes: strike shots; contact sheet.
  - Gyory, Nicholas. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff110 Includes: close-up of Gyory.
  - Hainsworth, Ray. (Box 22, Folder 16)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff111 Includes: male portrait.
  - Hajewski, Walter J. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff112 Includes: Hajewski with 2 women.
  - Halfkenny, Gail (Local 667 Healthtex). (Box 22, Folder 18)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff113 Includes: woman in shop; contact sheet.
  - Hall, William C., 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff114 Includes: James Anderson and William Hall at St. Louis, Mo. Mall; Bill Hall, 11/77; speaking at San Antonio, TX joint board meeting; Bill Hall, GEB meeting 3/79.
  - Hallmark Haefele Emblem Co. (Tampa, FLA.) (Box 22, Folder 20)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff115 Includes: union backer t-shirt; rank & file organizing and negotiating committee.
  - Hambas, Nick., 1992 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff116 Includes: close-up, July 1992.
  - Hamelin, Gayce. (Box 22, Folder 22)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff117 Includes: woman's portrait.
  - Hanes (Galax, Va.), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff118 Includes: Stetin addresses rally; Wonderknit in-plant committee; contact sheet 12/79.
  - Harkin, Sen. Tom., 1991 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff119 Includes: Harkin rallying at Manchester Knitted Fashions, N.H. 1991; contact sheets.
  - Harper Square ACTWU Housing. (Box 22, Folder 25)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff120 Includes: Chicago housing, development.
  - Harris, David. (Box 22, Folder 26)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff121 Includes: family in office; close-up.
  - Harrell, Louis. (Box 22, Folder 27)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff122 Includes: Roanoke Rapids, N.C. Congressional hearings.
  - Harriman, Averell. (Box 22, Folder 28)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff123 Includes: portraits; group shots.
  - Hartke, Vance., 1972 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff124 Includes: speech at 1972 Convention.
  - Hart Marx- Columbus, Ohio. (Box 22, Folder 30)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff125 Includes: shop scenes; contact sheet; Hartmax Distribution Center.
  - Hathaway, William D. (Maine). (Box 22, Folder 31)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff126 Includes: portrait.
  - Hatters Strike. (Box 22, Folder 32)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff127 Includes: NY strike scenes.
  - Hawkins, Augustus (D-Cal.) (Box 22, Folder 33)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff128 Includes: man at desk; contact sheets.
  - Health. (Box 22, Folder 34)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff129 Includes: deodorants; industrial hygienist; mouthwash; contact sheets; human arteries; kids exercising; stroke victim; asbestos screening; mayonnaise; seriously ill child; nurse; nursing home shots; prescrip
  - Health Assistance Program. (Box 22, Folder 35)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff130 Includes: Local 246 officers.
  - Health Care Conference NY 1/1991. (Box 22, Folder 36)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff131 Includes: meeting; contact sheets.
  - Health Care Conference- Milwaukee, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff132 Includes: meeting; contact sheets.
  - Health Conference/NY, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff133 Includes: group shots; contact sheets.
  - Health Security Committee. (Box 22, Folder 39)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff134 Includes: Finley chairing meeting at ACTWU headquarters; Brandzel and Rostenkowski; contact sheet.
  - Health-Tex Demos, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff135 Includes: picketing; contact sheets.
  - Health-Tex (Redsville, NC) (Box 22, Folder 41)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff136 Includes: group shots.
  - Hebron Textile Hebron, SC, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff137 Includes: 1988 group shots; negatives.
  - Heckler, Margaret. (Box 22, Folder 43)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff138 Includes: contact sheet.
  - Hedgepath, Maureen. see Earl Potter folder for contact sheets. (Box 22, Folder 44)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff139
  - Henderson, Harriet. (Box 22, Folder 45)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff140 Includes: Group shots.
  - Hendrickson, Shirley. (Box 22, Folder 46)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff141 Includes: Floyd Fithian campaign.
  - Herman, Tony. (Box 22, Folder 47)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff142 Includes: installation.
  - Herriman, Tom. (Box 22, Folder 48)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff143 Includes: man reading Labor Unity.
  - Hershkowitz, Sam., 1959 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff144 Includes: 8th Convention speech; 1959 convention speech; Mendelowitz and Hershkowitz.
  - Hervey, Jean. (Box 22, Folder 50)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff145 Includes: portraits; speeches.
  - Higgins, George (MSGR.) (Box 22, Folder 51)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff146 Includes: Murray-Green-Meany award; contact sheet.
  - Highland Yarn. (Box 22, Folder 52)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff147 Includes: man at factory; contact sheets; workers.
  - Highlander Center, New Market, Tenn. (Box 22, Folder 53)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff148 Includes: man smoking; close-ups; Black men in mock bargaining session; contact sheets; singing.
  - Hightower, Jim. (Box 22, Folder 54)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff149 Includes: man speaking.
  - Highstown Rug., 1939 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff150 Includes: lockout Feb. 1939.
  - Hill, Herbert. (Box 22, Folder 56)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff151 Includes: Herb Hill, NAACP, at desk.
  - Hillman Foundation Awards, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff152 Includes: speaker; contact sheets.
  - Hillman Foundation Awards, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    -- Collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff153 Includes: speaker; contact sheets.
  - Hillman Foundation Awards, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff 154 -- Includes: May 1988 luncheon; Michael Harrington w/ Jack Sheinkman; contact sheets.
  - Hillman Foundation Awards, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff 155 Includes: speeches; Henry Weinstein portrait; Robert McNamara portrait; group shots: Morgan, Miller, Sallee, Weinstein, Drummond, O'Brien, Streeter, Finley, and Sheinkman; contact sheets.
  - Hillman Foundation Awards, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff 156 Includes: Bill Drummond head shot; contact sheets; speeches.
  - Hillman Foundation Awards- early years., 1966-1971 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff 157 Includes: Lillian Smith portrait; Canada group shot, 11/66; Edward Morgan speech; Hillman Awards 1971.
  - Hillman Foundation Awards- Judges. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff 158 Includes: Fred Cook; Mr. and Mrs. Harry L. Billings; Harvey Swados; Irving Gitlin; George R. Stewart; Sara Fritz; George Vicas; Ted Ayers; Wilma Dykeman and James Stokely.
  - Hillman Foundation Awards Luncheon., 1986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    -- collection re-housed - formerly - b4, ff 159 Includes: 1986 awards; Jane Elliott; speeches; contact sheets; Sheinkman, Fritz, Salisbury, Lanck, Sharkey, Hardin, Finley, Talbot, Ludlum, J. Miller; Sheinkman, Fritz, Ford, Lelyveld, Peters, Gallagher, Mo